easy-immune-health.com 2019-09-26

# Privacy Policy for Easy Immune Health.com

## 

Privacy Policy

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use this website, [Easy Immune Health.com](https://www.easy-immune-health.com/) as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. 

Here at [Easy Immune Health.com](https://www.easy-immune-health.com/) we strive to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.

## Personal Information

[Easy Immune Health.com](https://www.easy-immune-health.com/) collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number. 

This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries. 

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.

No medical information is collected or retained by Easy Immune Health except in the case of those that become private clients. Private Client Information is retained on a separate secure server meeting all regulations for the collection and storing of medical information and is not available to the general public.

Easy Immune Health is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com. 

## Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

Here at [Easy Immune Health.com](https://www.easy-immune-health.com/) we may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the site's pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie enables [Easy Immune Health.com](https://www.easy-immune-health.com/) to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.

Learn How I Built This Site  
With NO Web Building Experience [](http://www.sitesell.com/Kerri6.html)

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ click here](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.

We may serve third party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web site to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web site.

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

### Non-Personal Information

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

### Release of Information

If [Easy Immune Health .com](https://www.easy-immune-health.com/) is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.

### How You Can Correct or Remove Information

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please [Contact Us Directly ](https://www.easy-immune-health.com/Contact-Information.html) or use our Contact page.

### Updates and Effective Date

[Easy Immune Health.com](https://www.easy-immune-health.com/) reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.

### Funding

Easy Immune Health is a private site that is not owned by or is a subsidiary of any other corporation or business- nor does it receive funding from corporations or businesses of any sort. There are no conflicts of interest to disclose. 

### Agreeing to Terms

If you do not agree to the [Easy Immune Health.com](https://www.easy-immune-health.com/) Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.

### Disclaimer

[Easy Immune Health.com](https://www.easy-immune-health.com/) is designed for information and educational purposes for the general public and health care professionals only. No information supplied is designed to diagnose or treat any illness, disease or medical condition. Always seek the advice of a qualified medical professional before making any decisions regarding your health. Use of this site implies that you agree with the above, that you are under the care of a medical doctor and have had a full workup for your current medical condition. The internet is not a reliable source of medical information and doing your own due diligence along with a full medical examination is imperative if you have any medical problems, complaints or signs or symptoms of medical problems.
